

Francesco Giuseppe Leccese

Date of birth: 27/12/1986

Address: Via Generale Dalla Chiesa 24/a - Bari(ITA)

Mail: franekdev86@gmail.com

Phone number (PL): +48 518 335 163

Phone number (ITA): +39 327 096 3560

Front End Developer and Doctor in Marketing and Business Communication with six years of experiance working in an ICT company. I have completed my Bachelor's Degree in Marketing and Communication at "Università degli Studi di Bari" (Faculty of Economics and Commerce) and attended 1000+ hours coding bootcamp to learn new languages while sharpening existing skills. Ready to apply my passion for coding to a talented engeneering team to develop quality solutions. Enjoy working closely to team members to ensure workloads are effectively redirected to bottlenecks and personally picking up the slack when necessary. With passion for both personal growth and for web development.

Work Experience

12/2023 - ongoing

FRONT END DEVELOPER internship at Developing.it (Bari - Italy)

01/2023 - ongoing

FRONT END DEVELOPER (freelance)

My portfolio webpage: https://franekdev-portfolio.netlify.app

My github profile: https://github.com/Franek-86

08/2022 - 12/2022

FUĴĨTSU

IT CUSTOMER SERVICE TEAM MANAGER at Fujitsu (Łódź - Poland)

- · Coordinate the service desk team members in their daily duties of attending to clients who come to make inquiries and facilitate good customer service culture in team members
- Evaluate and assess service delivery performance metrics and carry out survey on clients to weigh the level of service delivery in the company
- Keep record of daily operations at the desk for tracking of customer needs, services rendered and future reference
- · Create a mode of operations to be adhered to by team members in order to maintain good routine and orderliness

- Delegate specific service desk responsibilities to team members to create specialization and increase service delivery pace
- · Review all client complaints, rectify issues and liaise with appropriate departments to handle complex issues in a bid to provide more effective solutions
- · Observe service desk operation techniques to determine how effective they are and implement new techniques when old ones are ineffective

09/2019 - 07/2021



IT CUSTOMER SERVICE EXPERT TECHNICIAN at Fujitsu (Łódź - Poland)

- · Analyze and resolve customer concerns and problems, diagnose the root cause, and document interactions.
- · Provide on-call and ongoing troubleshooting, technical, and hardware advice and suggestions.
- · Support remote and local upgrades, installations, and maintenance.

09/2017 - 08/2019



IT CUSTOMER SERVICES AGENT at Fujitsu (Łódź - Poland)

- · Providing IT support to users located worldwide
- · Handling of company's high severity impact incidents
- · Constant and enthusiastic participation to internal trainings (Excel, Networking, Assertive communication, ITIL, Time Managing)

DXC.technology

12/2016 - 06/2017

SENIOR ACCOUNTING ASSOCIATE in AP departament at DXC Technology (Łódź - Poland)

- · Accounts Payable in JDE
- · Invoice processing, handling invoices from the arrival to post.

01/2016 - 11/2016



JUNIOR ACCOUNTING ASSOCIATE in AR department at CONDUENT (Łódź - Poland)

- · Account Receivable in SAP
- DD/DC proposals
- MEC reporting according to strict directivess

09/2015 - 11/2015

CUSTOMER SERVICE ADVISOR SouthWestern Business Process Services Poland Sp. z o.o

02/01/2012 - 20/05/2014



ASSISTANT PRODUCER MEC Produzioni (Bari - Italy)

· Assistant producer of a prime time television programme "Striscia La Notizia".

Handling production of televised reports aired by Mediaset S.p.a on the Italian national channel "Canale 5". (2 years)

Education

- Responsive Web Design (freeCodeCamp.org certification) (b)
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (freeCodeCamp.org certification)
- HTML&CSS Tutorial and Projects Course 2023 (Flexbox&Grid)(Udemy certification)
- Javascript Tutorial and Projects Course (2023) (Udemy certification)
- React 18 Tutorial and Projects Course (2023) (Udemy certification)
- Node Tutorial and Projects Course (2023) (Udemy)
- Marketing and Communication Bachelor's Degree at "Università degli Studi di Bari"
- IC3 Internet and Computing Core Certification IC3
- Certificate of Attendance accredited by The British Council
- "Development of film product" education course at A. S. FORCINEMA (Rome Italy)
- High School Diploma in Science at "Liceo scientifico Enrico Fermi" (Bari Italy)

Computer Skills & Languages

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- **BOOTSTRAP**
- **JAVASCRIPT**
- **VANILLA.JS**
- **REACT.JS**
- **NODE.JS**
- **MONGODB**
- **GIT**
- MS Office programs (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook)
- Italian language (native)
- English language (fluent)

